var questions = [{
	"question": "The first mechanical computer designed by Charles Babbage was called ?",
	"option1": "Abacus",
	"option2": "Analytical Engine",
	"option3": "Calculator",
	"option4": "Processor",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "Which of the folowing is the most powerful type of computer ?",
	"option1": "Super-micro",
	"option2": "SUper Conductor",
	"option3": "Super computer",
	"option4": "Megaframe",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "What are programs that tell the computer what to do ?",
	"option1": "hardware",
	"option2": "cartridges",
	"option3": "software",
	"option4": "printers",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "When a meeting is conducted over communication lines on a TV-like device it is called: ?",
	"option1": "telecommuting",
	"option2": "electronic mail",
	"option3": "teleconferencing",
	"option4": "telemarketing",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "The arithmetic/logic unit of the computer: ?",
	"option1": "can compare numbers",
	"option2": "can add numbers",
	"option3": "is part of the central processing unit",
	"option4": "all of the above",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "To work with pictures or charts you use which productivity tool ?",
	"option1": "Spreadsheet",
	"option2": "Graphics",
	"option3": "Database",
	"option4": "Word processor",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "which is a single integrated circuit ?",
	"option1": "Gate",
	"option2": "Mother Board",
	"option3": "Chip",
	"option4": "CPU",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "C is ?",
	"option1": "A third generation high level language",
	"option2": "A machine language",
	"option3": "An assembly language",
	"option4": "All of the above",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "Web pages a written using ?",
	"option1": "FTP",
	"option2": "HTTP",
	"option3": "HTML",
	"option4": "URL",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "UNIVAC is an example of ?",
	"option1": "First generation computer",
	"option2": "Second generation computer",
	"option3": "Third generation computer",
	"option4": "Fourth generation computer",
	"answer": "1"

}];
